{
    "id": "f298c18ff1ff445892b3a6e13bd161cb",
    "title": "Ing Form or Infinitive",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I wouldn't .................................. a loan.",
            "description": "After advise, we use an ing form, if there is no object. If there is an object, we use an infinitive. ",
            "answers": [
                "advise to take",
                "advise taking",
                "advise you to take"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "e2b15a51e589474f8715da7296054ec6"
        },
        {
            "question": "We don't allow ......................... in the kitchen.",
            "description": "After allow we use an ing form if there is no object. If there is an object, we use an infinitive. ",
            "answers": [
                "smoking",
                "to smoke",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "90afd77d1eb34794880320360c5836f6"
        },
        {
            "question": "Guests are not allowed ............................ in the kitchen.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "smoking",
                "to smoke",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c940843a2afe4b15b4b413db0443b35e"
        },
        {
            "question": "We are proud ................................",
            "description": "The adjective proud can be followed by either an -ing form or an infinitive. ",
            "answers": [
                "to have won",
                "of having won",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "5544fc43044e486ab9b7b5c641eaa718"
        },
        {
            "question": "I tried ..................... the wheel, but my hands were stiff.",
            "description": "After try, we can use either an infinitive or an -ing form. ",
            "answers": [
                "changing",
                "to change",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "cd593db0fa3d43b9af6da23d7297c25e"
        },
        {
            "question": "I would like .............................. you something.",
            "description": "After would like, we use infinitives. ",
            "answers": [
                "to tell",
                "telling",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "bf161cd8885d45c9bf854cabba228daf"
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you like .............................?",
            "description": "We use an -ing form after like to make a general statement or to ask a general question about preferences. ",
            "answers": [
                "dancing",
                "to dance",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4faafd7d312642eea7f1f5d8f5b7d706"
        },
        {
            "question": "I slowly began ................................. what she said.",
            "description": "The verbs understand, realise and know are not normally used in the continuous form. ",
            "answers": [
                "understanding",
                "to understand",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "50a1d523157f44aca15a6a8406c38fa7"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am sorry .................................. my temper this morning.",
            "description": "Sorry about + ing is used to refer to past things one regrets. ",
            "answers": [
                "to lose",
                "about losing",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "16eaeedbcd86400b99b1ba88b497e836"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am not afraid ............................... the truth.",
            "description": "There is little or no difference between afraid of + ing or afraid + infinitive. ",
            "answers": [
                "of telling",
                "to tell",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "5f6adbb5408b426bb36aa0c24c098310"
        },
        {
            "question": "Sorry ............................ you waiting. We can start now.",
            "description": "Sorry + infinitive is used to apologize for current situations. ",
            "answers": [
                "to keep",
                "for keeping",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "54970d67907c4a1eb732ac0416ee2096"
        },
        {
            "question": "I hate .............................. on weekends.",
            "description": "After hate, both infinitives and ing forms can be used. ",
            "answers": [
                "to work",
                "working",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "f82aaac915f5410096892c81b555bad8"
        }
    ]
}